- Are you ready, kids?
- 孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
Kids:
Aye, aye, Captain!
孩子们：
是啊是啊，队长！
- I can't hear you.
- 我听不到你说话。
Kids:
Aye, aye, Captain!
孩子们：
是啊是啊，队长！
- ♪ Ohh... ♪
- ♪ 哦...♪
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
Kids:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
孩子们：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he ♪
- ♪ 吸水性和黄色
他是多孔的 ♪
kids:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
孩子们：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ If nautical nonsense
be something you wish ♪
- ♪ 如果航海废话
成为你想要的东西♪
kids:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
孩子们：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish ♪
- ♪ 然后落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通♪
kids: SpongeBob SquarePants!
- Ready?
孩子们：海绵宝宝！
- 准备好？
All:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
SpongeBob SquarePants!
- SpongeBob
- 海绵宝宝
SquarePants!
方裤！
[laughing]
[笑]
[flute plays]
[长笛演奏]
[waves crashing]
[海浪拍打]
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
- And now
"The Jellyson Group."
- 现在
“杰利森集团。”
- Good evening and welcome
to "The Jellyson Group,"
- 晚上好，欢迎光临
到“杰利森集团”，
Bikini Bottom's best and
only show about jellyfishing.
比基尼泳裤最好的和
只展示有关水母的内容。
My guests tonight
are jellyfishing fashion
今晚我的客人
是水母时尚
journalist Fabrica Olay.
记者法布里卡·欧莱。
- [slurps]
- [啜饮]
Hmph.
哼。
- Famed jellyfish
juggler Fish-O The Clown.
- 著名的水母
杂耍者 Fish-O 小丑。
[honks horn]
[按喇叭]
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
嗯嗯。嗯嗯。
And something
called a SpongeBob.
还有一些东西
称为海绵宝宝。
- [babbles]
- [胡言乱语]
- Tonight we will be discussing
the moon jellyfish.
- 今晚我们将讨论
月亮水母。
Only seen once every 25
years, will soon be migrating
每 25 只出现一次
年，很快就会迁移
through Bikini Bottom.
通过比基尼底部。
- If I can just interrupt,
there's no evidence
- 如果我能打断的话
没有证据
this jellyfish even exists.
这种水母甚至存在。
Has anyone seen it,
much less caught it?
有谁看过吗，
更何况抓到了呢？
- Kevin C. Cucumber,
the greatest
- 凯文·C·黄瓜，
最伟大的
jellyfisher who ever lived,
caught the moon jellyfish.
曾经生活过的水母，
捕获了月亮水母。
Roll his famous
moon catching clip.
滚他著名的
捕捉月亮的剪辑。
- [laughs]
- [笑]
I caught it!
我抓住了！
I caught the moon jellyfish!
我抓到了月亮水母！
I love jellyfishing!
我喜欢捉水母！
- That video is a fake.
- 那个视频是假的。
- Well, it looked real to me.
- 嗯，对我来说它看起来很真实。
[horn honking]
[喇叭鸣响]
That fish is real...
- It's a fake! A ruse!
那条鱼是真的……
- 这是假的！诡计！
- You big-shoed buffoon.
- Anyone could see it.
- 你这个大鞋小丑。
- 任何人都可以看到它。
- The moon jellyfish is a fact.
- 月亮水母是事实。
- Stop!
- 停止！
It's not fake, and I'll prove
it to you by catching the moon
这不是假的，我会证明的
抓住月亮给你
jellyfish just like Kevin did.
像凯文一样的水母。
[laughter]
[笑声]
What did I tell you, Gary?
我告诉你什么了，加里？
Maybe if I can get
Kevin to help me,
也许如果我能得到
凯文来帮助我，
I'll have a chance to
catch that moon jellyfish.
我将有机会
抓住那只月亮水母。
And I know just
where to find Kevin.
我知道只是
哪里可以找到凯文.
At the Jellyspotters Clubhouse.
在 Jellyspotters 俱乐部会所。
Ooh.
哦。
[doorbell rings]
[门铃响]
- Meep.
- 米普。
Meep meep.
米普米普。
- Hello.
- 你好。
I'm looking for...
我在找...
- Meep.
- 米普。
Meep.
米普。
[regal music]
[富丽堂皇的音乐]
- Kevin, is it really you?
- 凯文，真的是你吗？
I'm not worthy.
我不值得。
- Hey there, Not Worthy.
- 嘿，不值得。
I'm Patrick.
我是帕特里克。
- Patrick?
- 帕特里克？
You're the president
of the Jellyspotters Club?
你是总统
Jellyspotters 俱乐部的成员？
- Sure am.
- 当然是。
We drew straws, and I was the
first one to eat them all.
我们抽了稻草，我就是那个
第一个把它们全部吃掉的人。
- That's great.
- 那太棒了。
Is Kevin Cucumber here?
凯文·黄瓜在吗？
- You mean the guy that
looks like a nerdy pickle?
- 你是说那个人
看起来像一个书呆子泡菜？
He got kicked out
of the club years
他被赶出了家门
俱乐部年数
ago and mysteriously
disappeared.
以前和神秘地
消失了。
No one knows where he is.
没有人知道他在哪里。
Huh?
啊？
But if you want to find him,
here's his current address.
但如果你想找到他
这是他现在的地址。
- 123 Shack in the Woods Lane.
- 林巷小屋 123 号。
Thank you, Patrick.
谢谢你，帕特里克。
- That's President
Patrick to you, Sonny Jim.
- 那是总统
帕特里克给你，桑尼·吉姆。
Can I get a refill on these?
我可以补充这些吗？
- Well, these are the woods,
- 嗯，这些是树林，
and this is the only lane I see.
这是我看到的唯一的车道。
[thunder booming]
[雷霆轰鸣]
This must be the place.
一定是这个地方。
Uh... oh!
呃……哦！
Hello?
你好？
Kevin?
凯文？
You here?
你在这里？
[screams]
[尖叫声]
Oh, phew.
哦，唷。
- [groans]
- [呻吟]
- [screams]
- [尖叫]
- [sneezes]
- [打喷嚏]
- Time for walkies,
Miss Marigold.
- 步行时间，
玛丽戈尔德小姐。
Huh?
啊？
- Um, uh...
- 嗯，呃...
hello, ma'am.
你好，女士。
I'm looking for
Kevin C. Cucumber.
我正在寻找
凯文·C·黄瓜。
Have you seen him?
你见过他吗？
- Eh, uh...
- 呃，呃...
- [screaming]
- [尖叫]
- Ahh!
- 啊！
Oh, Kevin?
哦，凯文？
- SpongeBob?
- 海绵宝宝？
- Kevin!
- 凯文！
- What are you doing here at
my secret forest shame hole?
- 你在这儿做什么
我的秘密森林耻辱洞？
- Looking for you, silly.
- 正在找你，傻瓜。
I need some moon
jellyfish-catching tips
我需要一些月亮
捕捉水母的技巧
from the master.
来自大师。
- Master?
- 掌握？
Ha!
哈!
I've lost any skills
I might have once had.
我失去了任何技能
我可能曾经有过。
I don't remember how to
catch a regular jelly.
我不记得怎么做
抓住普通的果冻。
I don't even remember
how to catch a cold.
我什至不记得了
如何感冒。
[sobbing]
[抽泣]
- Well, don't worry, Kevin.
- 好吧，别担心，凯文。
I can get you back in shape.
我可以让你恢复体形。
Then we can catch
the moon jelly,
然后我们就可以抓住
月光果冻，
and then you'll be on top again.
然后你就会再次登顶。
- [blows nose]
- [擤鼻子]
- Just like the old days.
- 就像过去一样。
- You think so?
- 你这么认为吗？
It's worth a try.
值得一试。
Thanks, SpongeBob.
谢谢，海绵宝宝。
This is the best day
I've had in years.
这是最好的一天
我已经有很多年了。
- Um, maybe we'll
clean you up first.
- 嗯，也许我们会
先把你清理干净。
Hmm.
唔。
[razor buzzing]
[剃须刀嗡嗡声]
- [groans]
- [呻吟]
- Kevin is back, baby.
- 凯文回来了，宝贝。
- Now that you're
looking the part,
- 现在你是
寻找零件，
let's shake the rust off those
jellyfishing skills, shall we?
让我们把那些铁锈抖掉
捕水母技能，可以吗？
- Hmm.
- 唔。
[jellyfish buzzing]
[水母嗡嗡声]
[laughs]
[笑]
[yells]
[喊叫]
[jellyfish zapping]
[水母的攻击]
- Ooh.
- 哦。
Maybe we'll start with
something a little easier.
也许我们会从
一些更容易的事情。
[jellyfish cooing]
[水母咕咕叫]
Jelly babies.
果冻宝宝们。
[jellyfish zapping]
[水母的攻击]
OK, maybe something
a lot easier.
好吧，也许有什么
容易多了。
- [yelps]
- [尖叫声]
Now, go ahead, Kevin.
现在，继续吧，凯文。
Ow!
Take your... ow! best swing.
噢！
带上你的……噢！最好的挥杆。
- Mm-hmm.
- 嗯嗯。
I did it!
我做到了！
I'm a jellyfisher again!
我又变回水母了！
[laughs]
[笑]
- OK, now for the real deal.
- 好吧，现在开始真正的交易了。
What's step one in catching
the moon jellyfish?
捕捉的第一步是什么
月亮水母？
- Uh, I know this one.
- 呃，我知道这个。
Wait for the moon
to come out so we can see it.
等月亮
出来让我们可以看到它。
[yelps]
[尖叫声]
- Ooh, good step one.
- 哦，第一步很好。
Here it comes.
它来了。
[giggles]
[咯咯笑]
[mystical music]
[神秘音乐]
♪ ♪
[jellyfish humming]
[水母嗡嗡声]
Ah!
啊!
OK, Kevin, what's step two?
好的，凯文，第二步是什么？
Kevin?
凯文？
- [screaming]
- [尖叫]
- Tire the moon jelly out
by getting it to chase us.
- 让月亮果冻疲惫不堪
让它追我们。
That must be step two, huh?
这一定是第二步，对吧？
- There is no step two.
- 没有第二步。
I don't know how to
catch a moon jellyfish.
我不知道该怎么做
捕获月亮水母。
I faked the moon
catching on a soundstage
我伪造了月亮
赶上音场
so people would
think I was cool.
所以人们会
觉得我很酷。
I got it.
我得到了它。
Aw.
噢。
[sobbing]
[抽泣]
- This is your chance
to catch it and really be cool.
- 这是你的机会
抓住它，真的很酷。
Quick, in here.
快点，到这里。
Our best bet is to surround it.
我们最好的选择就是包围它。
You go left.
你向左走。
I'll go right.
我就往右走。
We'll catch it between us.
我们会在我们之间抓住它。
And remember, stealth is key.
请记住，隐身是关键。
[both yelling]
[两人大喊]
- Huh?
Ahh!
- 啊？
啊！
[both shouting]
[两人大喊]
[sirens wailing]
[警笛哀嚎]
- Some of us work
in the morning.
- 我们中的一些人工作
早上。
Come on!
快点！
[both screaming]
[两人尖叫]
all: Hey,
it's the moon jellyfish.
全体：嘿，
这是月亮水母。
Look at that.
看看那个。
[cheering]
[欢呼]
[jellyfish buzzing]
[水母嗡嗡声]
- I don't think
we're going to catch up
- 我不认为
我们会赶上的
to that jellyfish, SpongeBob.
到那个水母，海绵宝宝。
My knees are getting tired.
我的膝盖越来越累了。
[knee yawns]
[膝盖打呵欠]
- If we can't outrun it,
maybe we can trap it.
- 如果我们无法超越它
也许我们可以困住它。
But we'll need some bait.
但我们需要一些诱饵。
What would a moon
jellyfish like to eat?
月亮会是什么
海蜇喜欢吃什么？
Both: Cheese.
两者：奶酪。
- Hmm?
- 唔？
[slurps]
[啜饮]
- Freeze, moon jelly.
- 冷冻吧，月亮果冻。
- Prepare to be caught.
- 做好被抓住的准备。
Huh?
啊？
- [chuckles]
- [轻笑]
- We're losing the light.
- 我们正在失去光明。
The moon jelly's
going to disappear.
月光果冻的
将会消失。
- Losing the light, you say?
- Huh?
- 你说失去光明？
- 啊？
Maybe you could use
a little moonlight.
也许你可以使用
一点月光。
[triumphant music]
[胜利的音乐]
♪ ♪
[together]
Meep, meep, meep.
[一起]
米普，米普，米普。
- Look, it's working!
- 看，它起作用了！
- We need more moonlight!
- 我们需要更多的月光！
[horn honks]
[喇叭鸣响]
- Huh?
- 啊？
- Ahh!
- 啊！
Gah!
- Hyah!
嘎！
- 哈！
- We caught him.
- 我们抓住了他。
We did it, Kevin.
我们做到了，凯文。
We did it.
我们做到了。
Whoa!
哇！
- Sorry, SpongeBob.
- 对不起，海绵宝宝。
But there's no we about it.
但没有我们的事。
I'm the sole catcher
of the moon jellyfish.
我是唯一的捕手
月亮水母的。
[laughs]
[笑]
Wha?
Wait a minute.
世界卫生大会？
等一下。
Where are we going?
Where are you taking me?
我们要去哪里？
你要带我去哪里？
[screams]
[尖叫声]
[together]
Ooh.
[一起]
哦。
- Wow.
- 哇。
- Where's the moon jelly going?
- 月光果冻去哪儿了？
- Home, Patrick.
- 回家，帕特里克。
Home.
家。
Until it comes back
in 25 years, that is.
直到它回来
25年后，也就是说。
- [screaming]
- [尖叫]
- [giggling]
- [咯咯笑]
- I hate jellyfishing.
- 我讨厌捕水母。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
- [giggling]
- [咯咯笑]
OK, Sandy, your surprise is
just a few more steps away.
好吧，桑迪，你的惊喜是
再走几步。
- Gosh, fellas,
I can't wait to...
- 天哪，伙计们，
我等不及...
both: Surprise!
两人：惊喜！
- [gasps] The Museum of
Bikini Bottom History!
- [喘气] 博物馆
比基尼泳裤的历史！
How'd y'all know
to take me here?
你们怎么知道的
带我来这里？
- You gave us these invitations.
- 你给了我们这些邀请。
- Bleh-ehh.
- 哎呀。
- And boy am I glad I did.
- 我很高兴我这么做了。
I'm just itching to learn
all about the rich history
我只是渴望学习
关于丰富的历史
of Bikini Bottom.
的比基尼底部。
And I will be taking notes.
我会做笔记。
My research
is going to be featured
我的研究
将会被推荐
in a scientific journal,
"The Naval Gazette."
在一本科学杂志上，
《海军公报》。
- I love gazing at my navel.
- 我喜欢凝视我的肚脐。
Hi.
你好。
Well, what are we waiting for?
那么，我们还等什么？
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
- Tickets, please.
- 请买票。
- Here you go.
- 干得好。
- [groans] Let's see here.
- [呻吟] 让我们看看这里。
One, two... gee,
I lost my place.
一、二……哎呀，
我失去了我的位置。
- Look, the first artifact.
- 看，第一件神器。
Bikini Bottom's
oldest security guard.
比基尼泳裤
最年长的保安。
- They should dust
these old robots.
- 他们应该除尘
这些老机器人。
- Hey, can't you read?
- 嘿，你不会读书吗？
It says no touching.
说的是不能碰。
- [laughs]
- [笑]
Sorry.
对不起。
- All right, youngsters.
- 好吧，年轻人。
In you go.
你进去吧。
Now, don't cause any trouble,
现在，不要惹任何麻烦，
or you'll have to answer to me.
否则你就得回答我。
[laughs]
[笑]
Hello?
你好？
[snoring]
[打鼾]
- Welcome to the ancient
past before Bikini
- 欢迎来到远古
比基尼之前的过去
Bottom was Bikini Bottom.
下装是比基尼下装。
They say the exhibits
here date back
他们说展品
这里追溯到
at least one gazillion years.
至少有亿万年。
- Uh, you sure about that math?
- 呃，你确定数学吗？
- Uh, they do math good.
- 呃，他们数学学得很好。
- [gasps]
- [喘气]
Look here, fellas.
看这里，伙计们。
Millions of years ago,
this here land
数百万年前，
这片土地
was called Bikini Top.
被称为比基尼上衣。
The elevation was lowered
due to natural erosion.
海拔降低了
由于自然侵蚀。
- [scoffs]
- [嘲笑]
That's not how it happened.
事情并非如此。
- Don't worry, Sandy.
- 别担心，桑迪。
We'll tell you the true story.
我们会告诉你真实的故事。
- Yeah.
It goes like this.
- 是的。
事情是这样的。
A gazillion years
ago, Bikini Top
亿万年
前，比基尼上衣
was hit by a humongous anchor.
被一个巨大的锚击中。
- The anchor flattened
the hill to the bottom
- 锚变平
山到山脚
of the ocean, which is why
it's called Bikini Bottom.
海洋的存在，这就是为什么
它被称为比基尼泳裤。
- And then the
anchor was so heavy
- 然后是
锚是如此重
that a bunch of buildings got
popped up out of the ground.
一堆建筑物
从地里冒出来。
[hawk cawing]
[鹰叫]
- Ah!
- Ooh!
- 啊！
- 哦！
- Bikini Bottom.
- 比基尼下装。
[both hooting]
[双方齐鸣]
- You mean to tell me
the very anchor
- 你是想告诉我
锚
we're standing
inside now is the one
我们站着
现在里面就是那个
that created Bikini Bottom?
创造了比基尼泳裤？
Both:
Uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh.
两者：
嗯嗯嗯嗯。
- Yup.
- 是的。
I see.
我懂了。
[elevator dings]
[电梯叮叮声]
Looks like this
floor covers Bikini
看起来像这样
地板套 比基尼
Bottom's old pioneer days.
底部的老拓荒者时代。
- Wow.
- 哇。
A genuine antique rock.
真正的古董岩石。
The pioneers used to ride
these babies for miles.
拓荒者们曾经骑过
这些婴儿绵延数英里。
- I want to try.
- 我想尝试一下。
Giddyup.
吉迪普。
[rock neighing]
[岩石嘶鸣]
Whoa.
哇哦。
Hey, calm down.
嘿，冷静点。
- I gotcha.
- 我明白了。
- [screaming]
- [尖叫]
- Whoo-hoo!
Yippee-yo-ki-yay.
- 呼呼！
Yippee-yo-ki-yay。
- Hey, no trick ropin'.
- 嘿，没有什么花招。
Darn hooligans.
该死的流氓。
[rock neighing]
[岩石嘶鸣]
Oh!
哦！
- Heh-heh-heh.
Sorry, sir.
- 嘿嘿嘿。
对不起，先生。
- Look, Sandy,
in the old days, the pioneers
- 看，桑迪，
过去，先驱者们
used to milk dairy urchins
on their homesteads.
用于给海胆挤奶
在他们的家园。
- [whistling]
- [吹口哨]
It was a simple, honest life
without an ounce of greed.
这是一种简单而诚实的生活
没有一丝贪婪。
- Another full pail, Bessie.
- 又满一桶，贝西。
I reckon I can barter
for quite a bit with this.
我想我可以以物易物
对此已经有相当多的时间了。
[chuckles]
Ah!
[笑声]
啊！
Maybe for some thicker gloves.
也许需要一些更厚的手套。
- But the pioneers
have to watch out
- 但是先驱们
必须要小心
for those dirty, stinky outlaws.
对于那些又脏又臭的不法之徒。
- [gasps] Oh, no.
- [喘气]哦，不。
It's the Grungy Gang.
这是蹩脚帮。
Oh, I knew something
smelled fishy.
哦，我知道了一些事情
闻起来有鱼腥味。
- [cackles]
- [咯咯笑]
We're here to take
that valuable little urchin
我们来这里是为了带走
那个可贵的小顽童
off your hands.
离开你的手。
Er, claws.
呃，爪子。
- Not so fast,
you filthy felons.
- 没那么快，
你们这些肮脏的重罪犯。
- Fortunately, Sheriff Pants
and Deputy Star brought
- 幸运的是，警长裤
和副星带来了
law and order to the land.
法律和秩序的土地。
We're here to clean up your act.
我们来这里是为了纠正你的行为。
- Get 'em, boys.
- 抓住他们，孩子们。
[cackling]
[咯咯笑]
- Huh?
- 啊？
- Aw, bubbles.
- 噢，泡泡。
- And with law came commerce.
- 伴随着法律而来的是商业。
- Thus Bikini Bottom's
first restaurant was opened.
- 因此比基尼泳裤
第一家餐厅开业。
The Krusty Kreamery.
库斯蒂·克里默里。
[both slurping]
[两人都发出咕噜声]
- Care for some souvenir milk?
- 想要一些纪念牛奶吗？
- I'm not thirsty.
- 我不渴。
Thanks.
- Suit yourself.
谢谢。
- 适合你自己。
[gulping]
[吞咽]
Ahh.
啊。
[elevator dings]
[电梯叮叮声]
- I reckon we've stepped
into Bikini Bottom's
- 我想我们已经迈出了一步
进入比基尼泳裤
Industrial Revolution era.
工业革命时代。
Wow.
哇。
A Model C Boat?
C型船？
Says here... ahh!
说到这里……啊！
- Don't read that, Sandy.
- 别读那个，桑迪。
We'll tell you the real story.
我们会告诉你真实的故事。
SpongeBob, what's the story?
海绵宝宝，故事是什么？
- Well, Bikini Bottom's own
titan of industry, Mr. Puff,
- 嗯，比基尼泳裤自己的
工业巨头普夫先生，
ran the first successful
boat assembly line.
第一次跑成功了
船装配线。
[horn honking]
[喇叭鸣响]
It was important for
every worker to perform
这对于
每个工人都要执行
as efficiently as possible.
尽可能高效。
[horns honking]
[喇叭鸣响]
[whistle blows]
[哨声响起]
- Speed up line number five.
- 加快第五行的速度。
Both:
Speeding up line number five.
两者：
加快五号线的速度。
- Huh?
- 啊？
[horns honking]
[喇叭鸣响]
- [babbling]
- [胡言乱语]
- Eh, eh... ahh!
- 呃，呃……啊！
- Sometimes they'd get
a little too caught up
- 有时他们会得到
有点太着迷了
in their work.
在他们的工作中。
Watch this.
注意这个。
- Whee!
- 呼！
[babbling]
[胡说]
Whoa.
哇哦。
- Oof!
- Ohh!
- 噢！
- 哦！
But being a shrewd
industrialist,
但作为一个精明的人
实业家,
Mr. Puff also owned
the hospital next door.
普夫先生还拥有
隔壁的医院。
- Beep, beep.
- 嘟嘟，嘟嘟。
- Now hold it just
a darn minute.
- 现在握住它
该死的一分钟。
- [laughs]
- [笑]
- Ain't no way these
screwball stories are true.
- 这些都不是办法
荒唐的故事是真的。
Let me read that plaque.
让我读一下那块牌匾。
"Titan of industry."
“工业巨头”。
"Assembly line."
“流水线。”
"Injuries."
“受伤。”
"Hospital next door."
“隔壁的医院。”
"Beep beep"?
“嘟嘟”？
Well, twist my tail.
好吧，扭动我的尾巴。
Y'all were right.
你们都是对的。
- Told ya.
- 告诉过你了。
Beep beep.
嘟嘟嘟。
- I knew Bikini Bottom's
history would be colorful,
- 我知道比基尼泳裤
历史将是丰富多彩的，
but I'm starting to have
more questions than answers.
但我开始有
问题多于答案。
- Maybe this question
mark on the top floor
- 也许这个问题
在顶楼做标记
is where you get your
questions answered.
是你得到你的地方
问题得到解答。
- You forgot to push these.
- 你忘了推这些。
[elevator dings]
[电梯叮叮声]
[rock music]
[摇滚乐]
- Psychedelic Sea era.
- 迷幻海洋时代。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
Deep Disco era.
深度迪斯科时代。
[electronic music]
[电子音乐]
New Wave Nitwits era.
新浪潮白痴时代。
[bouncy upbeat music]
[欢快欢快的音乐]
Nautical Nonsense era.
航海废话时代。
- This sure is a weird museum.
- 这确实是一个奇怪的博物馆。
[elevator dings]
[电梯叮叮声]
- Huh.
- 嗯。
I guess this
is the ghost exhibit.
我猜这个
是鬼魂展览。
- I think it's under
construction, Patrick.
- 我认为它在下面
建筑，帕特里克.
- Oh.
- 哦。
I can't wait till they
put the ghosts in.
我等不及他们了
把鬼魂放进去。
- [gasps]
- [喘气]
Wait a second.
等一下。
Is this a denture applicator?
这是假牙涂抹器吗？
[machine chomping]
【机器咀嚼】
Orthopedic jet boots.
矫形喷气靴。
The atomic adult diaper ray.
原子成人尿布射线。
Whoa!
哇！
Both: We're adults.
两人：我们都是成年人了。
[laughter]
[笑声]
- What in tarnation?
- 塔尼翁什么？
[gasps] This ain't no regular
future, fellas.
[喘气]这不是常规的
未来，伙计们。
This is a future ruled
by Old Man Walker!
这是一个被统治的未来
作者：老沃克！
[dramatic music]
[戏剧音乐]
[statue crumbling]
[雕像倒塌]
- That's right, you hooligans.
- 没错，你们这些流氓。
I said no touching!
我说了不许碰！
[together]
Sorry.
[一起]
抱歉。
[shuddering]
[颤抖]
- You three have seen too much,
and now I'm going to get ya.
- 你们三个看太多了，
现在我要去找你了。
Stay right there.
呆在那里。
[all screaming]
[所有人尖叫]
- Run!
- 跑步！
[yelling]
[大喊]
- Please, Old Man Walker.
- 拜托，老沃克。
We won't tell nobody
about the future.
我们不会告诉任何人
关于未来。
- Hey, everybody,
we've seen the future,
- 嘿，大家，
我们已经看到了未来，
but it's a secret.
但这是一个秘密。
Shh.
嘘。
[loud rumbling]
[巨响]
[all gasping]
[全都喘气]
- Uh-oh.
- 呃哦。
[all screaming]
[所有人尖叫]
- Old Man Walker
will rule you all.
- 老沃克
将统治你们所有人。
- Well,
there goes Bikini Bottom's
- 嗯，
比基尼泳裤就在那里
entire past and future.
整个过去和未来。
- So, Sandy, what'd you think?
- 那么，桑迪，你觉得怎么样？
- I'm still skeptical.
- 我仍然持怀疑态度。
Bikini Bottom's
past was a bit too nuts
比基尼泳裤
过去有点太疯狂了
for this old squirrel.
为了这只老松鼠。
- But hey, at least Bikini
Bottom is normal now.
- 但是嘿，至少比基尼
现在底部已经正常了。
- [yelling]
- [大喊]
- [cackling]
- [咯咯笑]
- Yep, totally normal.
- 是的，完全正常。